module.exports = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Who was the winner of season 1 of RuPaul's Drag Race?",
    "true_answer": "Bebe Zahara Benet",
    "false_answer1": "Trixie Mattel",
    "false_answer2": "Courtney Act",
    "false_answer3": "Kim Chi",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Reality TV"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Who won season 4 of Top Chef?",
    "true_answer": "Stephani Izard",
    "false_answer1": "Richard Blais",
    "false_answer2": "Michael Voltaggio",
    "false_answer3": "Melissa King",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Reality TV"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Who won season 1 of American Idol?",
    "true_answer": "Kelly Clarkson",
    "false_answer1": "Carrie Underwood",
    "false_answer2": "Fantasia Barrino",
    "false_answer3": "Jordin Sparks",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Reality TV"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Who won season 1 of Making It?",
    "true_answer": "Khiem Nguyen",
    "false_answer1": "Jo Gick",
    "false_answer2": "Amber Kemp-Gerstel",
    "false_answer3": "Billy Kheel",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Reality TV"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Who won season 4 of Project Runway?",
    "true_answer": "Christian Siriano",
    "false_answer1": "Jay McCarroll",
    "false_answer2": "Jeffrey Sebelia",
    "false_answer3": "Kentaro Kameyama",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Reality TV"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Who won the 2020 Men's French Open tennis tournament?",
    "true_answer": "Rafael Nadal",
    "false_answer1": "Novak Djokovic",
    "false_answer2": "Diego Schwartzman",
    "false_answer3": "Stefanos Tsitsipas",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Who won the 2020 Men's US Open tennis tournament?",
    "true_answer": "Dominic Thiem",
    "false_answer1": "Alexander Zverev",
    "false_answer2": "Pablo Careno Busta",
    "false_answer3": "Daniil Medvedev",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Who won the 2020 Women's French Open tennis tournament?",
    "true_answer": "Iga Swiatek",
    "false_answer1": "Sofia Kenin",
    "false_answer2": "Nadia Podoroska",
    "false_answer3": "Petra Kvitova",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Who won the 2020 Women's US Open tennis tournament?",
    "true_answer": "Naomi Osaka",
    "false_answer1": "Victoria Azarenka",
    "false_answer2": "Serena Williams",
    "false_answer3": "Jennifer Brady",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which team won the 2020 NBA Finals?",
    "true_answer": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "false_answer1": "Miami Heat",
    "false_answer2": "Boston Celtics",
    "false_answer3": "Denver Nuggets",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which team won the 2020 MLB World Series?",
    "true_answer": "Los Angeles Dodgers",
    "false_answer1": "Tampa Bay Rays",
    "false_answer2": "Houston Astros",
    "false_answer3": "Atlanta Braves",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Which team won the 2020 WNBA Championship?",
    "true_answer": "Seattle Storm",
    "false_answer1": "Las Vegas Aces",
    "false_answer2": "Minnesota Lynx",
    "false_answer3": "Connecticut Sun",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Who won the 2020 Men's U.S. Open golf tournament?",
    "true_answer": "Bryson DeChambeau",
    "false_answer1": "Collin Morikawa",
    "false_answer2": "Dustin Johnson",
    "false_answer3": "Matthew Wolff",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Who won the 2020 Women's British Open golf tournament?",
    "true_answer": "Sophia Popov",
    "false_answer1": "Thidapa Suwannapura",
    "false_answer2": "Minjee Lee",
    "false_answer3": "Inbee Park",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Which television show won the 2020 Emmy Award for Outstanding Comedy Series?",
    "true_answer": "Schitt's Creek",
    "false_answer1": "The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel",
    "false_answer2": "The Good Place",
    "false_answer3": "Curb Your Enthusiasm",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Which television show won the 2020 Emmy Award for Outstanding Drama Series?",
    "true_answer": "Succession",
    "false_answer1": "Better Call Saul",
    "false_answer2": "The Crown",
    "false_answer3": "Killing Eve",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Which television show won the 2020 Emmy Award for Outstanding Competition Program?",
    "true_answer": "RuPaul's Drag Race",
    "false_answer1": "The Masked Singer",
    "false_answer2": "Top Chef",
    "false_answer3": "The Voice",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Which movie won Best Picture at the 2020 Academy Awards?",
    "true_answer": "Parasite",
    "false_answer1": "Joker",
    "false_answer2": "Little Women",
    "false_answer3": "The Irishman",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Who won Best Actor at the 2020 Academy Awards?",
    "true_answer": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "false_answer1": "Leonardo DiCaprio",
    "false_answer2": "Antonio Banderas",
    "false_answer3": "Adam Driver",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Who won Best Actress at the 2020 Academy Awards?",
    "true_answer": "Renee Zellweger",
    "false_answer1": "Scarlett Johansson",
    "false_answer2": "Saoirse Ronan",
    "false_answer3": "Charlize Theron",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Who won Best Supporting Actor at the 2020 Academy Awards?",
    "true_answer": "Brad Pitt",
    "false_answer1": "Tom Hanks",
    "false_answer2": "Anthony Hopkins",
    "false_answer3": "Al Pacino",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Who won Best Supporting Actress at the 2020 Academy Awards?",
    "true_answer": "Laura Dern",
    "false_answer1": "Kathy Bates",
    "false_answer2": "Scarlett Johansson",
    "false_answer3": "Florence Pugh",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Which artist won Best Record at the 2020 Grammy Awards?",
    "true_answer": "Billie Eilish",
    "false_answer1": "Ariana Grande",
    "false_answer2": "Lizzo",
    "false_answer3": "Bon Iver",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Which artist won Best Album at the 2020 Grammy Awards?",
    "true_answer": "Billie Eilish",
    "false_answer1": "Lana Del Rey",
    "false_answer2": "Bon Iver",
    "false_answer3": "Lizzo",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What was the name of the first Atlantic hurricane of 2020?",
    "true_answer": "Hanna",
    "false_answer1": "Marco",
    "false_answer2": "Cristobal",
    "false_answer3": "Vicky",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": 2020
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "When was Diet Coke first put on the market?",
    "true_answer": 1982,
    "false_answer1": 1886,
    "false_answer2": 1963,
    "false_answer3": 1929,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Grace"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "What is the primary protein of an Impossible Burger?",
    "true_answer": "Soy",
    "false_answer1": "Seitan",
    "false_answer2": "Lentils",
    "false_answer3": "Quinoa",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Grace"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "What is the capital of Thailand?",
    "true_answer": "Bangkok",
    "false_answer1": "Pattaya City",
    "false_answer2": "Kuala Lampur",
    "false_answer3": "Chiang Mai",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Grace"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "How many Grammy Awards has Dolly Parton won?",
    "true_answer": 11,
    "false_answer1": 9,
    "false_answer2": 7,
    "false_answer3": 5,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Grace"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "What was the name of Adore Delano's first studio album?",
    "true_answer": "Till Death Do Us Party",
    "false_answer1": "After Party",
    "false_answer2": "Whatever",
    "false_answer3": "I Adore You",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Grace"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "In what city is Syracuse University located?",
    "true_answer": "Syracuse, NY",
    "false_answer1": "New York, NY",
    "false_answer2": "Rochester, NY",
    "false_answer3": "Albany, NY",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Grace"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "Which of these is not a shade of yellow?",
    "true_answer": "Carnelian",
    "false_answer1": "Aureolin",
    "false_answer2": "Ecru",
    "false_answer3": "Jasmine",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Grace"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "Which of these Wigs by Vanity hair colors is blonde?",
    "true_answer": "The Shade of RuPaul",
    "false_answer1": "Miss Venezuela",
    "false_answer2": "Dallas Sunset",
    "false_answer3": "April Foils",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Grace"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "Which of these products is always vegan?",
    "true_answer": "Oreos",
    "false_answer1": "White Sugar",
    "false_answer2": "Grapefruit Juice",
    "false_answer3": "Marshamallows",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Grace"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "What is the oldest continuously spoken language in the world?",
    "true_answer": "Tamil",
    "false_answer1": "Gaelic",
    "false_answer2": "Hebrew",
    "false_answer3": "Greek",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Grace"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "What is the capital of Cameroon?",
    "true_answer": "Yaounde",
    "false_answer1": "Abuja",
    "false_answer2": "N'Djamena",
    "false_answer3": "Bangui",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Jules"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "What is the largest city in Cameroon?",
    "true_answer": "Douala",
    "false_answer1": "Yaounde",
    "false_answer2": "Garoua",
    "false_answer3": "Kousseri",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Jules"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "Which of these colors is not in the flag of Cameroon?",
    "true_answer": "White",
    "false_answer1": "Red",
    "false_answer2": "Yellow",
    "false_answer3": "Green",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Jules"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "Which country was the first in Africa to reach the quarterfinals of the FIFA World Cup?",
    "true_answer": "Cameroon",
    "false_answer1": "Egypt",
    "false_answer2": "South Africa",
    "false_answer3": "Senegal",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Jules"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "What is the nickname of Cameroon's national football team?",
    "true_answer": "Les Lions Indomptables",
    "false_answer1": "Les Lions de la Téranga",
    "false_answer2": "Les Eléphants Heureux",
    "false_answer3": "La Citrouille Violette",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Jules"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "What is the French word for FOSSIL?",
    "true_answer": "Fossile",
    "false_answer1": "Facile",
    "false_answer2": "Fosily",
    "false_answer3": "Fosil",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Jules"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "What is the French word for FIVE?",
    "true_answer": "Cinq",
    "false_answer1": "Cinco",
    "false_answer2": "Cinque",
    "false_answer3": "Cinci",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Jules"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "What is the French word for DENTIST?",
    "true_answer": "Dentiste",
    "false_answer1": "Dentisierre",
    "false_answer2": "Dents",
    "false_answer3": "Dentista",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Jules"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "What is the French word for DOG?",
    "true_answer": "Chien",
    "false_answer1": "Koer",
    "false_answer2": "Hundo",
    "false_answer3": "Mbwa",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Jules"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "What is the French word for WINE?",
    "true_answer": "Vin",
    "false_answer1": "Vinho",
    "false_answer2": "Fion",
    "false_answer3": "Divai",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Jules"
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "question": "Who is the current Editor of the New York Times Crossword?",
    "true_answer": "Will Shortz",
    "false_answer1": "Margaret Farrar",
    "false_answer2": "Will Weng",
    "false_answer3": "Eugene T. Maleska",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "question": "What is the capital of Michigan?",
    "true_answer": "Lansing",
    "false_answer1": "Detroit",
    "false_answer2": "Grand Rapids",
    "false_answer3": "Canton",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "question": "Who is the youngest man to have ever won an ATP title?",
    "true_answer": "Aaron Krickstein",
    "false_answer1": "Michael Chang",
    "false_answer2": "Lleyton Hewitt",
    "false_answer3": "Boris Becker",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "question": "At an average price of $600 per pound, what is the world's most expensive cheese?",
    "true_answer": "Pule",
    "false_answer1": "White Stilton Gold",
    "false_answer2": "Caciocavallo Podolico",
    "false_answer3": "Old Ford",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "question": "Priced at $500,000 per bottle, what is the world's most expensive wine?",
    "true_answer": "1992 Screaming Eagle Cabernet",
    "false_answer1": "1945 Jeroboam of Chateau Mouton-Rothschild",
    "false_answer2": "1947 Cheval Blanc",
    "false_answer3": "1869 Chateau Lafite",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "question": "Which of these cars was not manufacted by Ford?",
    "true_answer": "Dart",
    "false_answer1": "Escort",
    "false_answer2": "Nucleon",
    "false_answer3": "Mondeo",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "question": "What is the state flower of Michigan?",
    "true_answer": "Apple Blossom",
    "false_answer1": "Wild Prarie Rose",
    "false_answer2": "Scarlet Carnation",
    "false_answer3": "Michigan Laurel",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "question": "What is the state reptile of Michigan?",
    "true_answer": "Painted Turtle",
    "false_answer1": "Eastern Collared Lizard",
    "false_answer2": "Gopher Tortoise",
    "false_answer3": "Michigan Whiptail",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "question": "Which of these latin phrases translates to \"of the law as it should be?",
    "true_answer": "De Lege Ferenda",
    "false_answer1": "De Lege Idealus",
    "false_answer2": "De Lege Ratio",
    "false_answer3": "De Lege Perfectum",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "question": "What is the meaning of the name Alison?",
    "true_answer": "Child of Nobility",
    "false_answer1": "Beautiful Child",
    "false_answer2": "Child of Warriors",
    "false_answer3": "Faithful Child",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Mom"
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "question": "In what city is Colby College located?",
    "true_answer": "Waterville, ME",
    "false_answer1": "Colby, ME",
    "false_answer2": "Lewiston, ME",
    "false_answer3": "Brunswick, ME",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "George"
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "question": "Which of these is not a coding language?",
    "true_answer": "C$",
    "false_answer1": "C++",
    "false_answer2": "C#",
    "false_answer3": "CSS",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "George"
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "question": "Which of these movies was not produced by Studio Ghibli?",
    "true_answer": "Twiceborn",
    "false_answer1": "Spirited Away",
    "false_answer2": "Kiki's Delivery Service",
    "false_answer3": "My Neighbor Totoro",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "George"
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "question": "Which god was ruler of the Greek pantheon?",
    "true_answer": "Zeus",
    "false_answer1": "Hades",
    "false_answer2": "Hera",
    "false_answer3": "Poseidon",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "George"
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "question": "Which of these is not the name of a main character in the Harry Potter series?",
    "true_answer": "Sigmund",
    "false_answer1": "Harry",
    "false_answer2": "Ron",
    "false_answer3": "Hermione",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "George"
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "question": "Which of these dolphins is known for being heavily covered in scars?",
    "true_answer": "Risso's Dolphin",
    "false_answer1": "Bottlenose Dolphin",
    "false_answer2": "Guina Dolphin",
    "false_answer3": "Melon-Headed Dolphin",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "George"
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "question": "How many strings are there on a standard ukulele?",
    "true_answer": 4,
    "false_answer1": 3,
    "false_answer2": 5,
    "false_answer3": 6,
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "George"
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "question": "What note does the highest key play on a standard 88-key piano?",
    "true_answer": "C",
    "false_answer1": "D",
    "false_answer2": "E",
    "false_answer3": "B",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "George"
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "question": "Which of these is not one of the standard voice ranges?",
    "true_answer": "Piano",
    "false_answer1": "Soprano",
    "false_answer2": "Tenor",
    "false_answer3": "Alto",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "George"
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "question": "In tennis, what does \"deuce\" mean?",
    "true_answer": "40-40",
    "false_answer1": "Love-Love",
    "false_answer2": "2-2",
    "false_answer3": "2-0",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "George"
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "question": "Who's a good boy?",
    "true_answer": "Raku",
    "false_answer1": "Not Raku",
    "false_answer2": "Not Raku",
    "false_answer3": "Not Raku",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "question": "Who's a good girl?",
    "true_answer": "Sophie",
    "false_answer1": "Not Sophie",
    "false_answer2": "Not Sophie",
    "false_answer3": "Not Sophi",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "question": "In what country is the Eiffel Tower located",
    "true_answer": "France",
    "false_answer1": "UK",
    "false_answer2": "US",
    "false_answer3": "China",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "question": "Which of these numbers is the largest?",
    "true_answer": 12,
    "false_answer1": 6,
    "false_answer2": 3,
    "false_answer3": 0,
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "question": "Which of these numbers is the smallest?",
    "true_answer": 2,
    "false_answer1": 20,
    "false_answer2": 200,
    "false_answer3": "2,000",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "question": "Which letter comes first in the alphabet?",
    "true_answer": "A",
    "false_answer1": "E",
    "false_answer2": "Z",
    "false_answer3": "Q",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "question": "Which of these letters is a vowel?",
    "true_answer": "U",
    "false_answer1": "B",
    "false_answer2": "G",
    "false_answer3": "R",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "question": "Which of these numbers is odd?",
    "true_answer": 7,
    "false_answer1": 2,
    "false_answer2": 10,
    "false_answer3": 24,
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "question": "Who is the most beautiful woman in the world?",
    "true_answer": "Alison Humphrey",
    "false_answer1": "Angelina Jolie",
    "false_answer2": "Bella Hadid",
    "false_answer3": "Beyonce Knowles-Carter",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "question": "Which ocean is largest?",
    "true_answer": "Pacific",
    "false_answer1": "Atlantic",
    "false_answer2": "Indian",
    "false_answer3": "Arctic",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "question": "How many states are there in the US?",
    "true_answer": 50,
    "false_answer1": 48,
    "false_answer2": 49,
    "false_answer3": 51,
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "question": "Which of these is not a citrus?",
    "true_answer": "Seven",
    "false_answer1": "Orange",
    "false_answer2": "Lemon",
    "false_answer3": "Lime",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "question": "Which of these is not a mammal?",
    "true_answer": "Purple",
    "false_answer1": "Bear",
    "false_answer2": "Cat",
    "false_answer3": "Skunk",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "question": "2+2=?",
    "true_answer": 4,
    "false_answer1": 22,
    "false_answer2": 2,
    "false_answer3": "Pass",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "question": "Mixing red and blue produces what color?",
    "true_answer": "Purple",
    "false_answer1": "Red",
    "false_answer2": "Blue",
    "false_answer3": "Eighteen",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "question": "Which of these weights the most?",
    "true_answer": "100 lbs of Apples",
    "false_answer1": "1 lb of Oranges",
    "false_answer2": "No Pears",
    "false_answer3": "1/2 lb of Grapes",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "question": "What is Jenna Maroney's first name?",
    "true_answer": "Jenna",
    "false_answer1": "Maroney",
    "false_answer2": "Janet",
    "false_answer3": "Liz",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "question": "How are you?",
    "true_answer": "I'm Well. How Are You?",
    "false_answer1": "Fine.",
    "false_answer2": "Who's Asking?",
    "false_answer3": "None of Your Business.",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "question": "Who's a good boy?",
    "true_answer": "Raku",
    "false_answer1": "Not Raku",
    "false_answer2": "Not Raku",
    "false_answer3": "Not Raku",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "question": "Who's a good girl?",
    "true_answer": "Sophie",
    "false_answer1": "Not Sophie",
    "false_answer2": "Not Sophie",
    "false_answer3": "Not Sophi",
    "rating": "Cheap",
    "category": "Cheap"
  },
  {
    "id": 186,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a flavor of quark?",
    "true_answer": "Left",
    "false_answer1": "Top",
    "false_answer2": "Charm",
    "false_answer3": "Bottom",
    "rating": "Trick",
    "category": "Trick"
  },
  {
    "id": 187,
    "question": "In trinary, what is 111 + 122?",
    "true_answer": 1010,
    "false_answer1": 233,
    "false_answer2": 1000,
    "false_answer3": 300,
    "rating": "Trick",
    "category": "Trick"
  },
  {
    "id": 188,
    "question": "What is the first recorded usage of the acronym \"OMG\" to mean \"Oh My God?",
    "true_answer": 1917,
    "false_answer1": 1997,
    "false_answer2": 2007,
    "false_answer3": 1657,
    "rating": "Trick",
    "category": "Trick"
  },
  {
    "id": 189,
    "question": "Winston Churchill's mother, Lady Randolph Churchill, was born in what city?",
    "true_answer": "New York City",
    "false_answer1": "Birmingham",
    "false_answer2": "Boston",
    "false_answer3": "London",
    "rating": "Trick",
    "category": "Trick"
  },
  {
    "id": 190,
    "question": "Which of these cities is furthest west?",
    "true_answer": "Reno, NV",
    "false_answer1": "Los Angeles, CA",
    "false_answer2": "Albuquerque, NM",
    "false_answer3": "Boulder, CO",
    "rating": "Trick",
    "category": "Trick"
  },
  {
    "id": "",
    "question": "What is the word for the portion of toothpaste on top of a toothbrush?",
    "true_answer": "Nurdle",
    "false_answer1": "Swoop",
    "false_answer2": "Spool",
    "false_answer3": "Tribbon",
    "rating": "Trick",
    "category": "Trick"
  },
  {
    "id": "",
    "question": "Which of these is not a state of matter?",
    "true_answer": "Fluid",
    "false_answer1": "Solid",
    "false_answer2": "Plasma",
    "false_answer3": "Gas",
    "rating": "Trick",
    "category": "Trick"
  },
  {
    "id": "",
    "question": "According to the conspiracy theorist David Icke, the Queen of England is secretly what?",
    "true_answer": "A Lizard",
    "false_answer1": "A Russian Spy",
    "false_answer2": "A Clone",
    "false_answer3": "Dead",
    "rating": "Trick",
    "category": "Trick"
  },
  {
    "id": "",
    "question": "Studies show that people with which hair color can on average withstand much more pain than others?",
    "true_answer": "Red",
    "false_answer1": "Blonde",
    "false_answer2": "Brown",
    "false_answer3": "Black",
    "rating": "Trick",
    "category": "Trick"
  },
  {
    "id": "",
    "question": "What is the name of the tallest mountain on Earth?",
    "true_answer": "Mount Kea",
    "false_answer1": "Mount Everest",
    "false_answer2": "Mount Kilimanjaro",
    "false_answer3": "Denali",
    "rating": "Trick",
    "category": "Trick"
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "question": "What year was the first Thanksgiving?",
    "true_answer": 1621,
    "false_answer1": 1787,
    "false_answer2": 1776,
    "false_answer3": 1492,
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "question": "What is the scientific name for a Turkey?",
    "true_answer": "Meleagris Gallopavo",
    "false_answer1": "Pavo Cristatus",
    "false_answer2": "Columbidae Livia",
    "false_answer3": "Gallus Domesticus",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "question": "Which US President declared Thanksgiving an annual holiday?",
    "true_answer": "Abraham Lincoln",
    "false_answer1": "George Washington",
    "false_answer2": "Franklin D. Roosevelt",
    "false_answer3": "Grover Cleveland",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "question": "How does the Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade conclude?",
    "true_answer": "The Arrival of Santa Clause",
    "false_answer1": "A Giant Turkey Float",
    "false_answer2": "A Marching Band",
    "false_answer3": "A Snoopy Float",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "question": "Which US President was the first to officially pardon a turkey?",
    "true_answer": "Ronald Reagan",
    "false_answer1": "John F. Kennedy",
    "false_answer2": "Franklin D. Roosevelt",
    "false_answer3": "George H.W. Bush",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "question": "What are turkey chicks called?",
    "true_answer": "Poult",
    "false_answer1": "Squab",
    "false_answer2": "Cheeper",
    "false_answer3": "Colt",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "question": "What is the name for the red protuberance on the forehead of turkeys?",
    "true_answer": "Snood",
    "false_answer1": "Gizzard",
    "false_answer2": "Wattle",
    "false_answer3": "Gobble",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "question": "What state raises the most turkeys?",
    "true_answer": "Minnesota",
    "false_answer1": "North Carolina",
    "false_answer2": "Arkansas",
    "false_answer3": "California",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "question": "When was green bean casserole first created?",
    "true_answer": 1955,
    "false_answer1": 1945,
    "false_answer2": 1935,
    "false_answer3": 1925,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "question": "In what culture's mythology does the cornucopia appear?",
    "true_answer": "Greek",
    "false_answer1": "Gaelic",
    "false_answer2": "Norse",
    "false_answer3": "Wampanoag",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "question": "When is Thanksgiving celebrated in Canada?",
    "true_answer": "2nd Monday of October",
    "false_answer1": "3rd Thursday of October",
    "false_answer2": "2nd Monday of November",
    "false_answer3": "4th Thursday of November",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "question": "In what part of Australia is Thanksgiving celebrated, brought by American whaling ships?",
    "true_answer": "Norfolk Island",
    "false_answer1": "Heard Island",
    "false_answer2": "Archernar Island",
    "false_answer3": "Keeling Island",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "question": "What year was the first Thanksgiving NFL game?",
    "true_answer": 1920,
    "false_answer1": 1930,
    "false_answer2": 1910,
    "false_answer3": 1940,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "question": "What year was the first Thanksgiving football game?",
    "true_answer": 1876,
    "false_answer1": 1856,
    "false_answer2": 1896,
    "false_answer3": 1916,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "question": "Which Native American tribe celebrated the first Thanksgiving with the Pilgrims?",
    "true_answer": "Wampanoag",
    "false_answer1": "Mahican",
    "false_answer2": "Mohegan",
    "false_answer3": "Massachusett",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "question": "What percentage of Americans eat turkey on Thanksgiving?",
    "true_answer": 88,
    "false_answer1": 85,
    "false_answer2": 95,
    "false_answer3": 92,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "question": "What is the most popular pie on Thanksgiving?",
    "true_answer": "Apple Pie",
    "false_answer1": "Pumpkin Pie",
    "false_answer2": "French Silk Pie",
    "false_answer3": "Sweet Potato Pie",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "question": "Which former SNL cast member released a Thanksgiving song titled \"The Thanksgiving Song?",
    "true_answer": "Adam Sandler",
    "false_answer1": "Kristen Wiig",
    "false_answer2": "Ana Gasteyer",
    "false_answer3": "Amy Poehler",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "question": "What year was canned cranberry sauce first sold?",
    "true_answer": 1941,
    "false_answer1": 1931,
    "false_answer2": 1951,
    "false_answer3": 1961,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "question": "Which utensil was not used at the first Thanksgiving?",
    "true_answer": "Fork",
    "false_answer1": "Knife",
    "false_answer2": "Spoon",
    "false_answer3": "Chopsticks",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "question": "A full grown turkey has approximately how many feathers?",
    "true_answer": "3,500",
    "false_answer1": "3,000",
    "false_answer2": "2,500",
    "false_answer3": "4,000",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "question": "Who was the only US President to not celebrate Thanksgiving ?",
    "true_answer": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "false_answer1": "Richard Nixon",
    "false_answer2": "John F. Kennedy",
    "false_answer3": "John Adams",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "question": "Where were turkeys first domesticated?",
    "true_answer": "Mexico",
    "false_answer1": "Canada",
    "false_answer2": "United States",
    "false_answer3": "Turkey",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "question": "Which dance craze was named after the turkey?",
    "true_answer": "Turkey Trot",
    "false_answer1": "Turkey Twist",
    "false_answer2": "Turkey Hop",
    "false_answer3": "Turkey Dance",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "question": "In \"A Charlie Brown Christmas,\" who gets the wishbone?",
    "true_answer": "Woodstock",
    "false_answer1": "Charlie Brown",
    "false_answer2": "Snoopie",
    "false_answer3": "Lucy",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Thanksgiving"
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "question": "What was the first line ever spoken on 30 Rock?",
    "true_answer": "Whoa. Excuse me. There's a line, buddy.",
    "false_answer1": "Who's that?",
    "false_answer2": "Can I get a hot dog?",
    "false_answer3": "This fatsuit smells like cornchips.",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "30 Rock"
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "question": "Who is the main character of 30 Rock?",
    "true_answer": "Liz Lemon",
    "false_answer1": "Tina Fey",
    "false_answer2": "Leslie Knope",
    "false_answer3": "Lucy Ricardo",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "30 Rock"
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "question": "How many seasons did 30 Rock run?",
    "true_answer": 7,
    "false_answer1": 8,
    "false_answer2": 6,
    "false_answer3": 9,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "30 Rock"
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "question": "What year did 30 Rock premiere?",
    "true_answer": 2006,
    "false_answer1": 2009,
    "false_answer2": 2003,
    "false_answer3": 2000,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "30 Rock"
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "question": "Where did Liz Lemon grow up?",
    "true_answer": "White Haven, PA",
    "false_answer1": "Upper Darby, PA",
    "false_answer2": "Jenkintown, PA",
    "false_answer3": "Newtown Square, PA",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "30 Rock"
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "question": "How many Emmy Awards did 30 Rock win?",
    "true_answer": 11,
    "false_answer1": 0,
    "false_answer2": 5,
    "false_answer3": 14,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "30 Rock"
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "question": "In what film, based on a Kevin Grishman novel of the same name, did Jenna Maroney play Constance Justice?",
    "true_answer": "The Rural Juror",
    "false_answer1": "Urban Fervor",
    "false_answer2": "Kidnapped by Danger",
    "false_answer3": "Nightstalkers",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "30 Rock"
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "question": "What was the first line ever spoken on Parks and Rec?",
    "true_answer": "Hello. Hi. My name is Leslie Knope.",
    "false_answer1": "Miss Knope! There's a drunk stuck in the slide!",
    "false_answer2": "Government isn't just a boy's club anymore.",
    "false_answer3": "Thank you so much for coming. What an amazing turnout.",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Parks and Rec"
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "question": "Who is the main character of Parks and Rec?",
    "true_answer": "Leslie Knope",
    "false_answer1": "Amy Poehler",
    "false_answer2": "Liz Lemon",
    "false_answer3": "Lucy Ricardo",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Parks and Rec"
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "question": "How many seasons did Parks and Rec run?",
    "true_answer": 7,
    "false_answer1": 8,
    "false_answer2": 6,
    "false_answer3": 9,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Parks and Rec"
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "question": "What year did Parks and Rec premiere?",
    "true_answer": 2009,
    "false_answer1": 2006,
    "false_answer2": 2003,
    "false_answer3": 2012,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Parks and Rec"
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "question": "Where was Leslie Knope born?",
    "true_answer": "Eagleton, IN",
    "false_answer1": "Pawnee, IN",
    "false_answer2": "Muncie, IN",
    "false_answer3": "Snerling, IN",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Parks and Rec"
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "question": "How many Emmy Awards did Parks and Rec win?",
    "true_answer": 0,
    "false_answer1": 5,
    "false_answer2": 11,
    "false_answer3": 14,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Parks and Rec"
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "question": "What is the name of the celebrated mini-horse on Parks and Rec?",
    "true_answer": "Li'l Sebastian",
    "false_answer1": "Pondy Danza",
    "false_answer2": "Sargeant Peanut Butter",
    "false_answer3": "Latawnya",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Parks and Rec"
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "question": "What is the title of the first episode of I Love Lucy?",
    "true_answer": "The Girls Want to Go to a Nightclub",
    "false_answer1": "Be a Pal",
    "false_answer2": "The Diet",
    "false_answer3": "Lucy Thinks Ricky Is Trying to Murder Her",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "I Love Lucy"
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "question": "Who is the main character of I Love Lucy?",
    "true_answer": "Lucy Ricardo",
    "false_answer1": "Lucille Ball",
    "false_answer2": "Leslie Knope",
    "false_answer3": "Liz Lemon",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "I Love Lucy"
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "question": "How many seasons did I Love Lucy run?",
    "true_answer": 6,
    "false_answer1": 8,
    "false_answer2": 10,
    "false_answer3": 4,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "I Love Lucy"
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "question": "What year did I Love Lucy premiere?",
    "true_answer": 1951,
    "false_answer1": 1941,
    "false_answer2": 1946,
    "false_answer3": 1956,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "I Love Lucy"
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "question": "Where Ethel Mertz born?",
    "true_answer": "Albuquerque, NM",
    "false_answer1": "New York, NY",
    "false_answer2": "St. Olaf, MN",
    "false_answer3": "Jackson, WY",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "I Love Lucy"
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "question": "How many Emmy Awards did I Love Lucy win?",
    "true_answer": 5,
    "false_answer1": 0,
    "false_answer2": 11,
    "false_answer3": 14,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "I Love Lucy"
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "question": "What is the capital of Ohio?",
    "true_answer": "Columbus",
    "false_answer1": "Cleveland",
    "false_answer2": "Cincinnati",
    "false_answer3": "Dayton",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "question": "What is the largest city in Ohio?",
    "true_answer": "Columbus",
    "false_answer1": "Cleveland",
    "false_answer2": "Cincinnati",
    "false_answer3": "Dayton",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "question": "What is the state wildflower of Ohio?",
    "true_answer": "Large White Trillium",
    "false_answer1": "Oak-Leaf Hydrangea",
    "false_answer2": "Mountain Laurel",
    "false_answer3": "Cherokee Rose",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "question": "What is the state bird of Ohio?",
    "true_answer": "Northern Cardinal",
    "false_answer1": "American Goldfinch",
    "false_answer2": "Scissor-Tailed Flycatcher",
    "false_answer3": "Northern Mockingbird",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "question": "What is the state animal of Ohio?",
    "true_answer": "White-Tailed Deer",
    "false_answer1": "Groundhog",
    "false_answer2": "American Black Bear",
    "false_answer3": "Eastern Gray Squirrel",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "question": "What is the state insect of Ohio?",
    "true_answer": "Ladybug",
    "false_answer1": "Green Darner",
    "false_answer2": "Viceroy Butterfly",
    "false_answer3": "American Burying Beetle",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "question": "What is the state fruit of Ohio?",
    "true_answer": "Tomato",
    "false_answer1": "Blackberry",
    "false_answer2": "Strawberry",
    "false_answer3": "Pear",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "question": "What is the state beverage of Ohio?",
    "true_answer": "Tomato Juice",
    "false_answer1": "Milk",
    "false_answer2": "Lemonade",
    "false_answer3": "Whiskey",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "question": "What is the state tree of Ohio?",
    "true_answer": "Ohio Buckeye",
    "false_answer1": "Longleaf Pine",
    "false_answer2": "White Oak",
    "false_answer3": "American Elm",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "question": "How do you spell the name of the city popular known as \"Cincy?",
    "true_answer": "Cincinnati",
    "false_answer1": "Cinccinnati",
    "false_answer2": "Cincinati",
    "false_answer3": "Cincinatti",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "question": "What year did Ohio become a state?",
    "true_answer": 1803,
    "false_answer1": 1758,
    "false_answer2": 1855,
    "false_answer3": 1828,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "question": "What is Cleveland's MLB team?",
    "true_answer": "The Indians",
    "false_answer1": "The Reds",
    "false_answer2": "The Bengals",
    "false_answer3": "The Browns",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "question": "What is Cleveland's NBA team?",
    "true_answer": "The Cavaliers",
    "false_answer1": "The Blue Jackets",
    "false_answer2": "The Browns",
    "false_answer3": "The Bengals",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "question": "What is Columbus' NHL team?",
    "true_answer": "The Blue Jackets",
    "false_answer1": "The Cavaliers",
    "false_answer2": "The Bengals",
    "false_answer3": "The Browns",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "question": "What is Cincinnati's NFL team?",
    "true_answer": "The Bengals",
    "false_answer1": "The Browns",
    "false_answer2": "The Blue Jackets",
    "false_answer3": "The Reds",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Ohio"
  },
  {
    "id": 151,
    "question": "Who has spent the most weeks ranked #1 on the ATP tour?",
    "true_answer": "Roger Federer",
    "false_answer1": "Novak Djokovic",
    "false_answer2": "Peter Sampras",
    "false_answer3": "Ivan Lendl",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Tennis"
  },
  {
    "id": 152,
    "question": "Who has spent the most weeks ranked #1 on the WTA tour?",
    "true_answer": "Steffi Graff",
    "false_answer1": "Martina Navratilova",
    "false_answer2": "Serena Williams",
    "false_answer3": "Chris Evert",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Tennis"
  },
  {
    "id": 153,
    "question": "Who is the youngest person to be ranked #1 on the ATP tour?",
    "true_answer": "Lleyton Hewitt",
    "false_answer1": "Pete Sampras",
    "false_answer2": "Roger Federer",
    "false_answer3": "Rafael Nadal",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Tennis"
  },
  {
    "id": 154,
    "question": "Who is the youngest person to be ranked #1 on the WTA tour?",
    "true_answer": "Martina Hingis",
    "false_answer1": "Serena Williams",
    "false_answer2": "Venus Williams",
    "false_answer3": "Tracy Austin",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Tennis"
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "question": "Who is the first person to be ranked #1 on the ATP tour?",
    "true_answer": "Illie Nastase",
    "false_answer1": "John Newcombe",
    "false_answer2": "Jimmy Connors",
    "false_answer3": "Bjorn Borg",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Tennis"
  },
  {
    "id": 156,
    "question": "Who is the first person to be ranked #1 on the WTA tour?",
    "true_answer": "Chris Evert",
    "false_answer1": "Evonne Goolagong",
    "false_answer2": "Martina Navratilova",
    "false_answer3": "Tracy Austin",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Tennis"
  },
  {
    "id": 157,
    "question": "Who has won the most titles on ATP tour?",
    "true_answer": "Jimmy Conors",
    "false_answer1": "Roger Federer",
    "false_answer2": "Ivan Lendl",
    "false_answer3": "Rafael Nadal",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Tennis"
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "question": "Who has won the most titles on WTA tour?",
    "true_answer": "Martina Navratilova",
    "false_answer1": "Chris Evert",
    "false_answer2": "Steffi Graff",
    "false_answer3": "Margaret Court",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Tennis"
  },
  {
    "id": 159,
    "question": "When was the first Championships played at Wimbledon?",
    "true_answer": 1878,
    "false_answer1": 1906,
    "false_answer2": 1892,
    "false_answer3": 1882,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Tennis"
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "question": "Which of these is not one of the Grand Slams of Tennis",
    "true_answer": "Italian Open",
    "false_answer1": "The Championships",
    "false_answer2": "Roland Garros",
    "false_answer3": "US Open",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Tennis"
  },
  {
    "id": 161,
    "question": "What is the capital of Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "St. Paul",
    "false_answer1": "Minneapolis",
    "false_answer2": "Wayzata",
    "false_answer3": "Duluth",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 162,
    "question": "What is the largest city in Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Minneapolis",
    "false_answer1": "St. Paul",
    "false_answer2": "Wayzata",
    "false_answer3": "Duluth",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 163,
    "question": "What is the state flower of Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Showy Lady Slipper",
    "false_answer1": "Common Lady Slipper",
    "false_answer2": "Large-Flowered Trillium",
    "false_answer3": "Queen Anne's Lace",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 164,
    "question": "What is the state bird of Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Common Loon",
    "false_answer1": "Cardinal",
    "false_answer2": "Mallard Duck",
    "false_answer3": "Wood Duck",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 165,
    "question": "What is the state fish of Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Walleye",
    "false_answer1": "Northern Pike",
    "false_answer2": "Trout",
    "false_answer3": "Salmon",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 166,
    "question": "What is the state butterfly of Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Monarch",
    "false_answer1": "Arogo Skipper",
    "false_answer2": "Common Buckeye",
    "false_answer3": "Eastern Tiger Swallowtail",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 167,
    "question": "What is the state fruit of Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Honeycrisp Apple",
    "false_answer1": "Granny Smith Apple",
    "false_answer2": "Gala Apple",
    "false_answer3": "Golden Delicious",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "question": "What is the state muffin of Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Blueberry",
    "false_answer1": "Chocolate Chip",
    "false_answer2": "Banana Walnut",
    "false_answer3": "Bran",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 169,
    "question": "What is the state sport of Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Ice Hockey",
    "false_answer1": "Lacrosse",
    "false_answer2": "Tennis",
    "false_answer3": "Curling",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 170,
    "question": "What is Minnesota's state tree?",
    "true_answer": "Norway Pine",
    "false_answer1": "White Pine",
    "false_answer2": "Paper Birch",
    "false_answer3": "Sugar Maple",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 171,
    "question": "What is Minnesota's MLB team?",
    "true_answer": "The Twins",
    "false_answer1": "The Saints",
    "false_answer2": "The Royals",
    "false_answer3": "The White Sox",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 172,
    "question": "What is Minnesota's NBA team?",
    "true_answer": "The Timberwolves",
    "false_answer1": "The Lynx",
    "false_answer2": "The Bucks",
    "false_answer3": "The Lakers",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 173,
    "question": "What is Minnesota's NHL team?",
    "true_answer": "The Wild",
    "false_answer1": "The Avalanche",
    "false_answer2": "The Jazz",
    "false_answer3": "The Penguins",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 174,
    "question": "What is Minnesota's NFL team?",
    "true_answer": "The Vikings",
    "false_answer1": "The Bears",
    "false_answer2": "The Tigers",
    "false_answer3": "The Broncos",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 175,
    "question": "What is Minnesota's WNBA team?",
    "true_answer": "The Lynx",
    "false_answer1": "The Timberwolves",
    "false_answer2": "The Storm",
    "false_answer3": "The Liberty",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 176,
    "question": "What year did Minnesota become a state?",
    "true_answer": 1858,
    "false_answer1": 1868,
    "false_answer2": 1848,
    "false_answer3": 1878,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 177,
    "question": "How many lakes are in Minnesota",
    "true_answer": "11,842",
    "false_answer1": "10,000",
    "false_answer2": "21,781",
    "false_answer3": "15,291",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 178,
    "question": "What is the most common lake name in Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Mud Lake",
    "false_answer1": "Long Lake",
    "false_answer2": "Rice Lake",
    "false_answer3": "Birch Lake",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 179,
    "question": "What is the largest lake entirely within Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Red Lake",
    "false_answer1": "Mille Lacs",
    "false_answer2": "Leech Lake",
    "false_answer3": "Lake of the Woods",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 180,
    "question": "Which of these was not invented in Minnesota",
    "true_answer": "Splinter-Free Toilet Paper",
    "false_answer1": "Scotch Tape",
    "false_answer2": "Stapler",
    "false_answer3": "Rollerblades",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 181,
    "question": "What is the tallest building in Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "IDS Center",
    "false_answer1": "Capella Tower",
    "false_answer2": "Foshay Tower",
    "false_answer3": "US Bank Plaza",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 182,
    "question": "Which of these cities is not located in Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "Fargo",
    "false_answer1": "Moorehead",
    "false_answer2": "Climax",
    "false_answer3": "Twin Valley",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 183,
    "question": "What is the population of Wayzata, Minnesota?",
    "true_answer": "4,592",
    "false_answer1": "4,137",
    "false_answer2": "5,208",
    "false_answer3": "4,921",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 184,
    "question": "What does the meaning of the Dakota \"mní sóta\" from which Minnesota's name is derived?",
    "true_answer": "Clear Blue Water",
    "false_answer1": "Laughing Water",
    "false_answer2": "Crooked Water",
    "false_answer3": "Many Waters",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 185,
    "question": "What was the city of St. Paul known as before gaining its current name?",
    "true_answer": "Pig's Eye Landing",
    "false_answer1": "Minehaha Colony",
    "false_answer2": "East Bank Encampment",
    "false_answer3": "Lumberjack Crossroads",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "id": 191,
    "question": "Which gymnast as won the most World Championship gold medals?",
    "true_answer": "Simone Biles",
    "false_answer1": "Svetlana Khorkina",
    "false_answer2": "Nadia Comaneci",
    "false_answer3": "Olga Korbut",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 192,
    "question": "An Olympic gold medal is made mostly of what metal?",
    "true_answer": "Silver",
    "false_answer1": "Gold",
    "false_answer2": "Copper",
    "false_answer3": "Nickel",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 193,
    "question": "How old was the oldest Olympic medal winner?",
    "true_answer": 72,
    "false_answer1": 56,
    "false_answer2": 48,
    "false_answer3": 64,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 194,
    "question": "How many hours did the longest wrestling match in Olympic history last?",
    "true_answer": 11,
    "false_answer1": 3,
    "false_answer2": 7,
    "false_answer3": 15,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 195,
    "question": "In what country were the first Winter Olympics held?",
    "true_answer": "France",
    "false_answer1": "Switzerland",
    "false_answer2": "United States",
    "false_answer3": "Greece",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 196,
    "question": "How long is an Olympic marathon?",
    "true_answer": "26 miles and 385 yards",
    "false_answer1": "26 miles",
    "false_answer2": "27 miles",
    "false_answer3": "22 miles and 225 yards",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "question": "Which of these is not the color of one of the rings on the Olympic flag?",
    "true_answer": "Orange",
    "false_answer1": "Black",
    "false_answer2": "Green",
    "false_answer3": "Yellow",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 198,
    "question": "Who holds the current world record in the 100 m dash?",
    "true_answer": "Usain Bolt",
    "false_answer1": "Tyson Gay",
    "false_answer2": "Yohan Blake",
    "false_answer3": "Justin Gatlin",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 199,
    "question": "Who has won the most Olympic medals?",
    "true_answer": "Michael Phelps",
    "false_answer1": "Larisa Latynina",
    "false_answer2": "Edoardo Magiarotti",
    "false_answer3": "Simone Biles",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 200,
    "question": "Which country has won the most Olympic medals?",
    "true_answer": "United States",
    "false_answer1": "Soviet Union",
    "false_answer2": "Great Britain",
    "false_answer3": "France",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "question": "What is a perfect score in bowling?",
    "true_answer": 300,
    "false_answer1": 200,
    "false_answer2": 100,
    "false_answer3": 150,
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 202,
    "question": "How many points is a touchdown worth in American Football?",
    "true_answer": 6,
    "false_answer1": 7,
    "false_answer2": 2,
    "false_answer3": 3,
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 203,
    "question": "What is the name of the world's most prestigious bicycling race?",
    "true_answer": "Tour de France",
    "false_answer1": "Giro d'Italia",
    "false_answer2": "Vuelta a España",
    "false_answer3": "Giro Rosa",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 204,
    "question": "What is the name for the equipment a shuffleboard player uses to move discs?",
    "true_answer": "Cue",
    "false_answer1": "Pusher",
    "false_answer2": "Stick",
    "false_answer3": "Hammer",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 205,
    "question": "Which team has won the NBA Championships the most times?",
    "true_answer": "Boston Celtics",
    "false_answer1": "LA Lakers",
    "false_answer2": "Golden State Warriors",
    "false_answer3": "Chicago Bulls",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 206,
    "question": "Which of these is not a discipline in alpine skiing?",
    "true_answer": "Super Slalom",
    "false_answer1": "Slalom",
    "false_answer2": "Giant Slalom",
    "false_answer3": "Super Giant Slalom",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 207,
    "question": "Into how many periods is a hockey game divided?",
    "true_answer": 3,
    "false_answer1": 2,
    "false_answer2": 4,
    "false_answer3": 5,
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "question": "How many players are there per side in a women's lacrosse game?",
    "true_answer": 12,
    "false_answer1": 9,
    "false_answer2": 11,
    "false_answer3": 14,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "question": "What is the minimum number of points needed to win a game in Olympic table tennis?",
    "true_answer": 11,
    "false_answer1": 21,
    "false_answer2": 6,
    "false_answer3": 15,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 210,
    "question": "Which country has won the most Olympic gold medals in baseball?",
    "true_answer": "Cuba",
    "false_answer1": "United States",
    "false_answer2": "South Korea",
    "false_answer3": "Japan",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Sports"
  },
  {
    "id": 211,
    "question": "Mark Twain’s beloved characters Tom Sawyer and Huckleberry Finn reside in which state?",
    "true_answer": "Missouri",
    "false_answer1": "Mississippi",
    "false_answer2": "Alabama",
    "false_answer3": "Oklahoma",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 212,
    "question": "What is the address of Sherlock Holmes' apartment?",
    "true_answer": "221B Baker Street",
    "false_answer1": "42 Wallaby Way",
    "false_answer2": "17 Cherry Tree Lane",
    "false_answer3": "4 Privet Drive",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 213,
    "question": "In Charles Dickens’s Oliver Twist, what food does Oliver famously ask for more of when he says: “Please, Sir, I want some more?”",
    "true_answer": "Gruel",
    "false_answer1": "Soup",
    "false_answer2": "Stew",
    "false_answer3": "Bread",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 214,
    "question": "The Girl with the Dragoon Tattoo was originally published in which language?",
    "true_answer": "Swedish",
    "false_answer1": "Finnish",
    "false_answer2": "Danish",
    "false_answer3": "Norwegian",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 215,
    "question": "Truman Capote’s In Cold Blood takes its name from which Shakespeare play?",
    "true_answer": "Timon of Athens",
    "false_answer1": "Coriolanus",
    "false_answer2": "Troilus and Cressida",
    "false_answer3": "Titus Andronicus",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 216,
    "question": "Who is the hero of Douglas Adams’ Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy series?",
    "true_answer": "Arthur Dent",
    "false_answer1": "Paul Atreides",
    "false_answer2": "Winston Smith",
    "false_answer3": "Rick Deckard",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 217,
    "question": "Chronologically, which novel comes first in C. S. Lewis’s Chronicles of Narnia series?",
    "true_answer": "The Voyage of the Dawn Treader",
    "false_answer1": "The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe",
    "false_answer2": "The Magician's Nephew",
    "false_answer3": "The Silver Chair",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 218,
    "question": "What was the title of Agatha Christie's first published novel?",
    "true_answer": "The Mysterious Affair at Styles",
    "false_answer1": "The Murder on the Links",
    "false_answer2": "The Murder of Roger Ackroyd",
    "false_answer3": "The Seven Dials Mystery",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 219,
    "question": "Who wrote I Know Why the Caged Bird Sings?",
    "true_answer": "Maya Angelou",
    "false_answer1": "Audre Lord",
    "false_answer2": "Gwendolyn Brooks",
    "false_answer3": "Adrienne Rich",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 220,
    "question": "How many acts are there in Shakespeare's Romeo and Juliet?",
    "true_answer": 5,
    "false_answer1": 4,
    "false_answer2": 3,
    "false_answer3": 2,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 221,
    "question": "Which of these Shakespeare works is a comedy?",
    "true_answer": "Love's Labour's Lost",
    "false_answer1": "Timon of Athens",
    "false_answer2": "King Lear",
    "false_answer3": "MacBeth",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 222,
    "question": "Which of these Shakespeare works is a tragedy?",
    "true_answer": "Coriolanus",
    "false_answer1": "The Merchant of Venice",
    "false_answer2": "The Tempest",
    "false_answer3": "The Winter's Tale",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 223,
    "question": "How many of Shakespeare's plays were published during his lifetime?",
    "true_answer": 18,
    "false_answer1": 23,
    "false_answer2": 0,
    "false_answer3": 9,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 224,
    "question": "What is the best selling novel of all time?",
    "true_answer": "Don Quixote",
    "false_answer1": "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone",
    "false_answer2": "The Hobbit",
    "false_answer3": "Moby Dick",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 225,
    "question": "Who is the only author to publish books in 9 of the 10 Dewey Decimal categories?",
    "true_answer": "Isaac Asimov",
    "false_answer1": "Stephen King",
    "false_answer2": "R.L. Stine",
    "false_answer3": "Corin Tellado",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Literature"
  },
  {
    "id": 226,
    "question": "What was the first European name given to the city now called New York?",
    "true_answer": "New Angoulême",
    "false_answer1": "New Orange",
    "false_answer2": "New Holland",
    "false_answer3": "New Mallorca",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "New York"
  },
  {
    "id": 227,
    "question": "Which of these is not a borough of New York City?",
    "true_answer": "Long Island",
    "false_answer1": "Staten Island",
    "false_answer2": "Queens",
    "false_answer3": "Manhattan",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "New York"
  },
  {
    "id": 228,
    "question": "Which borough of New York City has the highest population?",
    "true_answer": "Brooklyn",
    "false_answer1": "Manhattan",
    "false_answer2": "The Bronx",
    "false_answer3": "Queens",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "New York"
  },
  {
    "id": 229,
    "question": "How many councilmembers are there on the New York City Council?",
    "true_answer": 51,
    "false_answer1": 5,
    "false_answer2": 100,
    "false_answer3": 21,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "New York"
  },
  {
    "id": 230,
    "question": "What is the tallest building in New York City?",
    "true_answer": "One World Trade Center",
    "false_answer1": "Central Park Tower",
    "false_answer2": "Empire State Building",
    "false_answer3": "Chrysler Building",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "New York"
  },
  {
    "id": 231,
    "question": "What percentage of the population of New York State lives in New York City?",
    "true_answer": 40,
    "false_answer1": 50,
    "false_answer2": 60,
    "false_answer3": 30,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "New York"
  },
  {
    "id": 232,
    "question": "Of the 41 Broadway theaters, how many are actually located on Broadway itself?",
    "true_answer": 3,
    "false_answer1": 10,
    "false_answer2": 23,
    "false_answer3": 0,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "New York"
  },
  {
    "id": 233,
    "question": "At 13,370 performances, what is the longest running show in Broadway history?",
    "true_answer": "The Phantom of the Opera",
    "false_answer1": "Chicago",
    "false_answer2": "The Lion King",
    "false_answer3": "Cats",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "New York"
  },
  {
    "id": 234,
    "question": "Which broadway show has the record for most Tony Award wins in a single season?",
    "true_answer": "The Producers",
    "false_answer1": "Hamilton",
    "false_answer2": "South Pacific",
    "false_answer3": "Cabaret",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "New York"
  },
  {
    "id": 235,
    "question": "In what burough is New York City's Chinatown?",
    "true_answer": "Manhattan",
    "false_answer1": "Brooklyn",
    "false_answer2": "Queens",
    "false_answer3": "The Bronx",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "New York"
  },
  {
    "id": 236,
    "question": "Which country accounts for more than half of the western coastline of South America",
    "true_answer": "Chile",
    "false_answer1": "Argentina",
    "false_answer2": "Peru",
    "false_answer3": "Brazil",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 237,
    "question": "Which country has the moast coastline",
    "true_answer": "Canada",
    "false_answer1": "China",
    "false_answer2": "United States",
    "false_answer3": "Russia",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 238,
    "question": "What percentage of the Nile river is located in Egypt?",
    "true_answer": 22,
    "false_answer1": 100,
    "false_answer2": 9,
    "false_answer3": 45,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 239,
    "question": "What is the oldest continuously inhabited city in the world?",
    "true_answer": "Damascus, Syria",
    "false_answer1": "Athens, Greece",
    "false_answer2": "Jerusalem, Israel",
    "false_answer3": "Shanghai, China",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 240,
    "question": "Which US state has the most active volcanoes?",
    "true_answer": "Alaska",
    "false_answer1": "Hawaii",
    "false_answer2": "California",
    "false_answer3": "Washington",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 241,
    "question": "Which continent is the flattest?",
    "true_answer": "Australia",
    "false_answer1": "Africa",
    "false_answer2": "South America",
    "false_answer3": "Antarctica",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 242,
    "question": "What city is the capital of Australia",
    "true_answer": "Canberra",
    "false_answer1": "Melbourne",
    "false_answer2": "Perth",
    "false_answer3": "Sydney",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 243,
    "question": "Which of these African nations is not landlocked",
    "true_answer": "Congo",
    "false_answer1": "Burkina Faso",
    "false_answer2": "Niger",
    "false_answer3": "Chad",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 244,
    "question": "What is the deepest point in Earth's oceans?",
    "true_answer": "Mariana Trench",
    "false_answer1": "Eurasian Basin",
    "false_answer2": "Java Trench",
    "false_answer3": "Tonga Trench",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 245,
    "question": "Which waterfall is the tallest on earth?",
    "true_answer": "Angel Falls",
    "false_answer1": "Tugela Falls",
    "false_answer2": "Waihilau Falls",
    "false_answer3": "Yosemite Falls",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 246,
    "question": "What is the tallest mountain in North America?",
    "true_answer": "Denali",
    "false_answer1": "Mount Rainier",
    "false_answer2": "Mount Rushmore",
    "false_answer3": "Mount Whitney",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 247,
    "question": "What is the easternmost state in the US?",
    "true_answer": "Alaska",
    "false_answer1": "Maine",
    "false_answer2": "Florida",
    "false_answer3": "New York",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 248,
    "question": "What is the westernmost state in the US?",
    "true_answer": "Alaska",
    "false_answer1": "Washington",
    "false_answer2": "Hawaii",
    "false_answer3": "California",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 249,
    "question": "What is the northernmost state in the US?",
    "true_answer": "Alaska",
    "false_answer1": "Washington",
    "false_answer2": "Minnesota",
    "false_answer3": "Maine",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 250,
    "question": "What is the southernmost state in the US?",
    "true_answer": "Hawaii",
    "false_answer1": "Texas",
    "false_answer2": "Florida",
    "false_answer3": "Alaska",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Geography"
  },
  {
    "id": 251,
    "question": "Which of these animals have fingerprints indistinguishable from humans?",
    "true_answer": "Koalas",
    "false_answer1": "Sun Bears",
    "false_answer2": "Lemurs",
    "false_answer3": "Komodo Dragons",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 252,
    "question": "Which fish swims slowest",
    "true_answer": "Seahorse",
    "false_answer1": "Jellyfish",
    "false_answer2": "Starfish",
    "false_answer3": "Trout",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 253,
    "question": "Which animals hold hands in order to prevent drifting apart while they sleep?",
    "true_answer": "Sea Otters",
    "false_answer1": "Platypuses",
    "false_answer2": "Beavers",
    "false_answer3": "Toads",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 254,
    "question": "Which of these animals is not a marsupial",
    "true_answer": "Echidnas",
    "false_answer1": "Koalas",
    "false_answer2": "Opposums",
    "false_answer3": "Kangaroos",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 255,
    "question": "Nils Olav is the only non-human to be knighted in Norway. What species of animal is Sir Olav?",
    "true_answer": "Penguin",
    "false_answer1": "Reindeer",
    "false_answer2": "Brown Bear",
    "false_answer3": "Beaver",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 256,
    "question": "Kaninhoppning is a Swedish show jumping competition for what animal?",
    "true_answer": "Rabbits",
    "false_answer1": "Horses",
    "false_answer2": "Dogs",
    "false_answer3": "Caribou",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 257,
    "question": "Social interaction is essential for guinnea pigs, so which country has made it illegal to own single guinnea pig?",
    "true_answer": "Switzerland",
    "false_answer1": "Canada",
    "false_answer2": "Finland",
    "false_answer3": "Australia",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 258,
    "question": "Dudley Coutts Marjoribanks was a 19th century Scottlish Lord responsible for developing the Golden Retreiver breed. What was his title?",
    "true_answer": "Baron Tweedmouth",
    "false_answer1": "Viscount of Owlpen",
    "false_answer2": "Lord Wrigglesworth",
    "false_answer3": "Duke of Earl",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 259,
    "question": "Which of these is not one of the three types of Golden Retreiver?",
    "true_answer": "French",
    "false_answer1": "British",
    "false_answer2": "American",
    "false_answer3": "Canadian",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 260,
    "question": "Weighing in at less than 3 grams, what is the world's smallest bird?",
    "true_answer": "Bee Hummingbird",
    "false_answer1": "Lesser Goldfinch",
    "false_answer2": "Willow Tit",
    "false_answer3": "Weebill",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 261,
    "question": "What is the term for a group of ferrets?",
    "true_answer": "A Business",
    "false_answer1": "An Army",
    "false_answer2": "A Conspiracy",
    "false_answer3": "A Party",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 262,
    "question": "What is the term for a group of lemurs?",
    "true_answer": "A Conspiracy",
    "false_answer1": "A Business",
    "false_answer2": "An Army",
    "false_answer3": "A Party",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 263,
    "question": "How do prairie dogs greet each other?",
    "true_answer": "A Kiss",
    "false_answer1": "A Yip",
    "false_answer2": "A Whistle",
    "false_answer3": "A Hop",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 264,
    "question": "In what country does the sovereign legally own all unmarked swans?",
    "true_answer": "The United Kingdom",
    "false_answer1": "France",
    "false_answer2": "Japan",
    "false_answer3": "North Korea",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 265,
    "question": "What is unique about the nine-banded armadillo?",
    "true_answer": "It always gives birth to identical quadruplets",
    "false_answer1": "Their shells are tougher than diamonds",
    "false_answer2": "They are the only mammals that live on Antarctica",
    "false_answer3": "One killed my mother",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Cute Animals"
  },
  {
    "id": 266,
    "question": "Which of these is not a Pokemon?",
    "true_answer": "Merolark",
    "false_answer1": "Pikachu",
    "false_answer2": "Bulbasaur",
    "false_answer3": "Charmander",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Video Games"
  },
  {
    "id": 267,
    "question": "Who is the protagonist of The Legend of Zelda?",
    "true_answer": "Link",
    "false_answer1": "Zelda",
    "false_answer2": "Impa",
    "false_answer3": "Ganondorf",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Video Games"
  },
  {
    "id": 268,
    "question": "Which of these consoles is sold Nintendo",
    "true_answer": "Switch",
    "false_answer1": "PS4",
    "false_answer2": "XBox One",
    "false_answer3": "Dreamcast",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Video Games"
  },
  {
    "id": 269,
    "question": "What was the first videogame system released to be used in conjunction with a television?",
    "true_answer": "Magnavox Odyssey",
    "false_answer1": "Mattel Intellivision",
    "false_answer2": "Sinclair ZX8",
    "false_answer3": "Atari 5200",
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Video Games"
  },
  {
    "id": 270,
    "question": "What is the name of the woman Mario is attempting to save from the eponymous ape in the original Donkey Kong?",
    "true_answer": "Pauline",
    "false_answer1": "Peach",
    "false_answer2": "Daisy",
    "false_answer3": "Toadstool",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Video Games"
  },
  {
    "id": 271,
    "question": "What species is Sonic the Hedgehog's sideckick, Tails?",
    "true_answer": "Fox",
    "false_answer1": "Hedgehog",
    "false_answer2": "Echidna",
    "false_answer3": "Dog",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Video Games"
  },
  {
    "id": 272,
    "question": "Which of these is not the name of one of the ghosts in Pac-Man?",
    "true_answer": "Zinky",
    "false_answer1": "Inky",
    "false_answer2": "Blinky",
    "false_answer3": "Pinky",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Video Games"
  },
  {
    "id": 273,
    "question": "What year was Tetris first released?",
    "true_answer": 1984,
    "false_answer1": 1980,
    "false_answer2": 1990,
    "false_answer3": 1976,
    "rating": "Hard",
    "category": "Video Games"
  },
  {
    "id": 274,
    "question": "What is the highest-grossing arcade game of all time?",
    "true_answer": "Pac-Man",
    "false_answer1": "Street Fighter II",
    "false_answer2": "Dance Dance Revolution",
    "false_answer3": "Space Invaders",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Video Games"
  },
  {
    "id": 275,
    "question": "The Kingdom Hearts video game series is a collaboartion between Square Enix and what famous company?",
    "true_answer": "Disney",
    "false_answer1": "DC Comics",
    "false_answer2": "Nintendo",
    "false_answer3": "Sony",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Video Games"
  },
  {
    "id": 276,
    "question": "What type of rock forms from lava and magma as it cools?",
    "true_answer": "Igneous",
    "false_answer1": "Sedimentary",
    "false_answer2": "Metamorphic",
    "false_answer3": "Nimbus",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Middle School Science"
  },
  {
    "id": 277,
    "question": "Which of these minerals ranks highest on the Mohs hardness scale?",
    "true_answer": "Topaz",
    "false_answer1": "Quartz",
    "false_answer2": "Calcite",
    "false_answer3": "Talc",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Middle School Science"
  },
  {
    "id": 278,
    "question": "Which periodic family do helium, neon, and krypton belong in?",
    "true_answer": "Noble Gases",
    "false_answer1": "Alkaline Metals",
    "false_answer2": "Earth Gases",
    "false_answer3": "Halogens",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Middle School Science"
  },
  {
    "id": 279,
    "question": "What does a plant cell have that an animal cell does not?",
    "true_answer": "Cell Wall",
    "false_answer1": "Nucleus",
    "false_answer2": "Mitochondria",
    "false_answer3": "Cytoplasm",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Middle School Science"
  },
  {
    "id": 280,
    "question": "Which of the following pH values indicate a neautral substance?",
    "true_answer": 7,
    "false_answer1": 14,
    "false_answer2": 0,
    "false_answer3": 10,
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Middle School Science"
  },
  {
    "id": 281,
    "question": "What was the first Disney feature film?",
    "true_answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarves",
    "false_answer1": "Pinocchio",
    "false_answer2": "Fantasia",
    "false_answer3": "Dumbo",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 282,
    "question": "Which of these characters is not an official Disney Princess?",
    "true_answer": "Tinker Bell",
    "false_answer1": "Ariel",
    "false_answer2": "Belle",
    "false_answer3": "Mulan",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 283,
    "question": "Which Disney film was the first to be entirely computer animated?",
    "true_answer": "Toy Story",
    "false_answer1": "Shrek",
    "false_answer2": "James and the Giant Peach",
    "false_answer3": "Finding Nemo",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 284,
    "question": "What year did Disneyland open?",
    "true_answer": 1955,
    "false_answer1": 1945,
    "false_answer2": 1965,
    "false_answer3": 1975,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 285,
    "question": "What is the name of Princess Ariel and Prince Eric's daughter in Disney's The Little Mermaid franchise?",
    "true_answer": "Melody",
    "false_answer1": "Ursula",
    "false_answer2": "Alana",
    "false_answer3": "Aquata",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 286,
    "question": "Which Disney princess sings \"Once Upon a Dream?",
    "true_answer": "Aurora",
    "false_answer1": "Belle",
    "false_answer2": "Snow White",
    "false_answer3": "Merida",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 287,
    "question": "What does \"Hakuna Matata\" mean?",
    "true_answer": "No Worries",
    "false_answer1": "Let's Eat",
    "false_answer2": "Party Time",
    "false_answer3": "Run Away",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 288,
    "question": "What was the name of Walt Disney's first animated character?",
    "true_answer": "Oswald the Rabbit",
    "false_answer1": "Mickey Mouse",
    "false_answer2": "Donald Duck",
    "false_answer3": "Bugs Bunny",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 289,
    "question": "What is the name of Belle's father in Disney's Beauty and the Beast?",
    "true_answer": "Maurice",
    "false_answer1": "Edward",
    "false_answer2": "Adam",
    "false_answer3": "Howard",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 290,
    "question": "Emperor Kuzco turns into what animal in The Emperor’s New Groove?",
    "true_answer": "Llama",
    "false_answer1": "Guinnea Pig",
    "false_answer2": "Camel",
    "false_answer3": "Kangaroo",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 291,
    "question": "How many dalmation puppies did Pongo and Perdita have?",
    "true_answer": 15,
    "false_answer1": 101,
    "false_answer2": 100,
    "false_answer3": 55,
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 292,
    "question": "Who composed the music for Disney's Tarzan?",
    "true_answer": "Phil Collins",
    "false_answer1": "Randy Newman",
    "false_answer2": "Alan Menken",
    "false_answer3": "Elton John",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 293,
    "question": "What is the name of Rapunzel's pet chameleon in Disney's Tangled?",
    "true_answer": "Pascal",
    "false_answer1": "Ace",
    "false_answer2": "Cam",
    "false_answer3": "Dusty",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 294,
    "question": "What is the name of Nemo's dad in Disney's Finding Nemo?",
    "true_answer": "Marlin",
    "false_answer1": "Nemo Sr.",
    "false_answer2": "Dory",
    "false_answer3": "Bruce",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 295,
    "question": "Which of these is not the name of a hyena in Disney's The Lion King?",
    "true_answer": "Fisi",
    "false_answer1": "Shenzi",
    "false_answer2": "Banzai",
    "false_answer3": "Ed",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 296,
    "question": "Which of these has never been the name of a step-sister in a Disney film?",
    "true_answer": "Edwina",
    "false_answer1": "Anastasia",
    "false_answer2": "Minerva",
    "false_answer3": "Doris",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 297,
    "question": "Which of these is not the name of a fairie in Disney's Sleeping Beauty?",
    "true_answer": "Felicia",
    "false_answer1": "Flora",
    "false_answer2": "Fauna",
    "false_answer3": "Merryweather",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 298,
    "question": "Which of these is not the name of a kitten in Disney's Aristocats?",
    "true_answer": "Rameau",
    "false_answer1": "Toulouse",
    "false_answer2": "Berlioz",
    "false_answer3": "Marie",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 299,
    "question": "What is the name of the \"Beast of Paradise Falls\" in Disney's Up?",
    "true_answer": "Kevin",
    "false_answer1": "Bart",
    "false_answer2": "Dug",
    "false_answer3": "Ed",
    "rating": "Medium",
    "category": "Disney"
  },
  {
    "id": 300,
    "question": "What type of animal is Eeyore from the Winnie the Pooh franchise?",
    "true_answer": "Donkey",
    "false_answer1": "Tiger",
    "false_answer2": "Owl",
    "false_answer3": "Rabbit",
    "rating": "Easy",
    "category": "Disney"
  }
]